ROB DODSON: Everyone, what's up?
Rob Dodson：大家好吗？
It's Rob Dodson.
这是Rob Dodson。
And in today's episode, we're going
在今天的一集中
to be picking up where we left off
我们将继续之前的工作
last time with the core toolbar.
它是主要的工具栏。
And we're going to be combining it with our new best
我们将和他一起成为我们最好的朋友，
friend, the core header panel to build
上主板
our very first application.
为了构建我们的第一个应用程序。
So let's check it out.
因此，让我们来看看它。
Now, the core header panel is the first element
现在，上层主板是第一个要素
we've touched upon that's going to give us
我们触及到的那将给我们
the beginnings of a full-blown application scaffold.
完整的应用程序平台的起点。
But before we dive into the header panel itself,
但是在进入顶部面板之前，
I want to take a moment to reflect
我想等一下
on where we're at this point.
关于我们此时的目标。
Now, so far, we've been learning each element
现在，直到这一刻，我们已经了解了所有要素
as a single-purpose building block.
作为单一用途的构建基块。
And the value in doing this is that, once you've
这样做的价值，
mastered a few of these building blocks,
一旦掌握了其中一些构建基块，
you can start to assemble them into different structures.
您可以开始将它们分为不同的结构。
You can think of this kind of in the same way
您可以考虑类似
that you put together all the bricks that make up a house.
用同样的方法收集砖块盖房子。
In the programming world, this is often
在编程世界中，
referred to as composition.
这通常称为语法。
And generally, I like to think of composition
通常，我会像
as taking one really big thing and assembling it out
取一些太大的东西并与
of a bunch of smaller single purpose pieces that are really
一小套单用途小品
easy to understand.
很容易理解。
That's basically what we're going
这就是我们要做的
to be doing with the core header panel
与上部主板
today and really just moving forward
从今天起
with Web Components in general.
Web组件整体。
So as we're working, I want you to keep
在工作时，我不想忘记安装的想法
that idea of composition in the back your head.
我记得很好。
I want you to see if you can pick up the places where we're
我要你尝试去接地方
taking simple building blocks and composing them together
我们采用简单的构建块并将它们放在一起
into these bigger, more complex structures.
在这些更大，更复杂的结构中。
So let's get started with the header panel.
因此，让我们从顶部面板开始。
Here's what we're planning to build today.
这就是我们今天计划建造的。
As you can see, we've got the beginnings
你看，我们有起点
of a really simple mobile application.
一个非常简单的移动应用程序。
Now, the core header panel by itself
现在，顶级主板本身
is really just a scaffold.
该平台仅代表。
It's got a header area up at the top which can hold something
它的顶部有一个标题区域，可能有一些东西
like a core toolbar.
如主工具栏。
And it's got a content area down below.
以及下面的内容区域。
One thing to note is that for the header panel to display,
要注意的一件事是显示顶部面板，
both it and its parent are going to need
她和她的出身将需要确定长度。
Now, this is a really common pitfall
这是一个真正的问题
for developers when they first start
对于开发人员，当他们第一次开始
working with the header panel.
使用顶部面板。
They'll drop the tag on the page,
他们会将标签放在页面上
but then, they won't see anything
但是然后，他们什么也看不到
showing up on their screen.
出现在屏幕上。
And that's because those heights aren't set.
这是因为未设置这些长度。
Even if the header panel had a default height in percents,
即使顶部面板的默认长度为百分比，
you still wouldn't see anything until you
你什么也看不到
give the parent, which in this case
因此，请提供原文（在这种情况下为正文），
Now, you can do this in CSS by setting the HTML and the body
现在，您可以在CSS中通过调整HTML和正文文本来执行此操作
to have a height of 100% and then,
长度为100％
telling the core header panel to have a height of 100% to match.
然后告诉顶部主板具有100％的长度来匹配它。
Or you can get a little fancy, and you
或者你可以得到一些装饰，
can just layout attributes do this with flexbox.
或者，您可以使用弹性框来计划属性以执行此操作。
And that's how we're going to do it.
这就是我们要走的路。
So we're going to use a layout attribute
我们将使用layout属性
and a vertical attribute.
和垂直属性。
And these are going that tell the body to lay out
这将告诉基本文字
its children vertically from top to bottom.
它的分支从上到下垂直。
And we're also going to tell our header
我们还将告诉我们的顶部面板
panel that we want it to flex.
我们希望它具有灵活性。
And that way it's going to try to fill as much of the screen
这样，您将尝试填充屏幕的最大区域
as it can.
尽可能地。
And you should also remember the full bleed attribute
您还应该记住full-margin属性
from our last video.
从我们以前的视频。
That's going to tell the body tag
这将告诉正文文本属性
to remove all of its margin and padding.
删除所有边距和填充。
And that way our content can go right up
这样我们的内容可以
to the edges of the screen.
它到达屏幕的边缘。
Now, to make our toolbar display,
现在，要显示工具栏，
we're just going to drop a core toolbar element into our header
我们只删除工具栏的主项
panel.
在顶部面板中。
And the cool thing is, the header panel is smart enough
很棒的是，顶部面板很聪明
to know that if it has a core toolbar child,
要知道，如果您有一个基本的分支工具栏，
it should just place it up here at the top of the screen.
它必须将其放在屏幕顶部的此处。
And by default, it's actually going to keep it pinned up.
默认情况下，您将其挂在这里。
There it's actually a sticky toolbar.
它实际上是一个稳定的工具栏。
And I'll show an example of what that looks like in just a bit.
接下来，我将向您展示一个示例。
Now, another thing to point out is
你应该知道的另一件事
that you don't have to use a core toolbar here
是您不必在这里使用基本工具栏吗
if you don't want to.
如果没有。
You could also use a div with the class of core header.
您还可以将div与标头类一起使用。
That would also get pinned to the top of the screen.
这也将安装在屏幕顶部。
Now, for the content inside of our header panel,
对于标题面板中的内容，
we're just going to drop a div on the page.
我们将在页面上放置一个div。
And I've just going ahead and filled it with some markup
我会去填补一点空白
and some shapes so that we have something
有些形状甚至构成了我们的东西
displayed in our application.
在我们的应用程序中显示。
And any child is not a core toolbar element
每个分支都不是基本的工具栏项
or doesn't have that core header class,
或没有基本的信笺，
it's going to end up displaying in this main content area
它将在此主要内容区域中呈现
down here.
在这
So you're not limited to just this one div.
因此，您的选择不仅限于一格。
You could have as many as you want.
您可以使用最适合您的电话号码。
Generally, I just put one here.
总的来说，我在这里放了一个。
That way I can give the content of my application
这样我就可以给我的应用程序内容
some consistent padding.
一些和谐的填充。
Now, the header panel's main job is
并且用于上面板的主要功能
to control the scrolling behavior on the page.
它们控制页面上的滑动行为。
So you'll see that, as the user's swiping on their phone,
您会看到，当用户移动手机时，
the toolbar stays pinned up the top of the document.
工具栏仍位于文档顶部。
And the content is sliding underneath it.
内容在其下方滑动。
Now, the thing to note here is that we're not
现在，您可以观察到
writing any CSS nor are we writing
我们不编写任何CSS或JavaScript样式
any JavaScript to make this happen.
发生
The header panel is just a smarter
顶部面板灵巧而真实
primitive that knows what to do when there's a core toolbar
了解有基本工具栏时的操作
inside of it.
里面
Now, if you want to change the behavior of our header panel,
如果您想更改顶部面板的行为，
it's really as simple as changing an attribute.
它很容易更改属性。
If we give it a mode attribute and set it to scroll,
如果我们给它一个状态属性并将其设置为滑动，
now, you'll see that, as the user is scrolling the page,
您会看到，当用户向下滚动页面时，
the toolbar moves with the rest of the content.
工具栏随内容的其余部分一起移动。
Now, there's a few other values that we can use for that mode.
在这种情况下，我们可以使用其他一些值。
But instead of just talking about it,
但是与其谈论，
how about we hop into our code editor
如果我们转到脚本编辑器怎么办
and actually get some of this showing up on screen.
我们将其中一些值显示在屏幕上。
So over on my terminal, I'm going
在去航站楼之前，
to write bower install, save, polymer/coreelements.
我将编写凉亭安装，保存，聚合物/共芯元素。
Now, that's actually going to go and fetch
现在，这将真的去看看
all the elements in the course set.
对于主要组中的所有项目。
And the reason I'm doing this is because when
我这样做的原因
I'm developing a site or an application,
是在我开发网站或应用程序时
it's just a lot easier to install everything in the set.
在组中安装所有内容要容易得多。
And that way I don't have to keep switching back and forth
这样我就不必继续切换
between my project and the terminal
在我的项目和终端之间
just to install a few more elements.
只是为了安装一些新物品。
Also, the only elements that are actually
而且只有元素
served in my application are the ones
那已经为我的申请服务了
that I've written HTML imports for.
是我为导入HTML而编写的。
So if you're OK with having all the elements
如果您不介意所有物品
on your local disk, this can be a really convenient way
在本地磁盘上，
to develop.
那将适合发展。
Switching to our code editor, we've
通过转换为脚本编辑器，
already laid out a basic application
我们已经开发了基本的应用程序
using the code from the previous slides.
使用上一张幻灯片中的脚本。
The first thing I'm going to do is,
我要做的第一件事
I'm going to create a file to hold all the imports that I'm
是创建一个文件来控制所有导入
going to use in my application.
我在我的应用中使用的。
So I'll pop open my sidebar, and I'll
所以我打开侧边栏，
create a new file called elements.html.
创建一个名为elements.html的新文件。
Now, I'm just going to paste in all the imports
现在，我将粘贴所有导入
that I'm going to use in this project.
我将在该项目中使用。
And really quickly, what I've got here is,
很快，我在这里的是
I've got a core header panel, a core toolbar, core icon
我有基本的横幅广告，基本的工具栏，基本的图标，
buttons, and core icons.html.
添加到核心icons.html。
And that's going to load in the definition for the core icon
这将在基本图标元素定义中加载
element as well as the default icon set.
除了默认图标集。
So save this.
因此保存。
And back in my index HTML file, I'm
回到HTML索引文件，
going to create an import to load in
我将创建一个导入来加载
that elements HTML file that I just created.
在刚创建的HTML元素文件中。
Now, this is going to do two things.
现在，这将做两件事。
It's going to keep the head tag on my index HTML
它将在HTML索引文件中保留标题标签
file nice and tidy.
精美而整洁。
It's also going to make it much easier to vulcanize
这将使其很容易部署
all my imports together when it's
我所有的进口货在一起
time to ship this into production.
过渡到生产时。
Now, taking a look down at the code,
看下面的脚本，
you'll see that it's basically the same thing
您会注意到它完全一样
that we had in the slides.
我们在幻灯片中。
We've got full bleed attribute and a few of the other layout
我们有完整的保证金属性和其他一些图表属性，
attributes like layout in vertical.
像垂直布局。
We've got our core header panel inside of here.
这里有基本的刊头面板。
And inside of that, we've got our core toolbar.
在其中，我们有基本的工具栏。
One thing to note is that down in my content div,
请注意，在内容div的底部，
if I pop this open, you'll see that there's
如果打开它，您会看到有一堆
a whole bunch of markup inside of here.
在这里编码。
This is just boilerplate that I've created,
这是您创建的标准文字，
so we can lay out a bunch of shapes
所以我们可以放一些形状
on the screen of our apps some content.
在屏幕上为我们的应用提供一些内容。
You don't actually need to worry about any
您不必担心脚本
of the code that's inside of this element.
在这个项目里面。
It's really just for presentation.
它仅用于显示。
Now, back in our terminal, I'm going
现在，回到终端，
to start up a local server, so we can preview the application.
我将运行本地服务器，以便我们可以预览该应用程序。
I'm going to do Python-m simple HTTP server
我将使用Python-m做一个简单的HTTP服务器
and run it on Port 9000.
并在端口9000上运行它。
You can use any local server that you want.
您可以使用任何所需的本地服务器。
I'm just using Python because it comes pre-installed on Macs.
我将使用Python，因为它已在Mac上就绪。
But if you want to start it in Node server or Apache server,
但是，如果您想在Node或Apache服务器上运行它，
all that will work just fine.
您不会遇到任何问题。
Now, hopping back into Chrome, if we open a page at Localhost
现在，回到Chrome，如果我们在本地9000服务器上打开一个页面，
We've got our toolbar up at the top,
我们的工具栏位于顶部，
and all our content is scrolling underneath it.
我们所有的内容都可以在下面访问。
So right now, the layout is really
目前的情况
designed for a mobile device.
该设计适合移动设备。
It's not so great on our desktop.
在计算机上不是很好。
If we want to actually preview this on our phone,
如果我们真的想在手机上显示它，
we can open up the Hamburger menu,
我们可以打开汉堡菜单，
and go down to More Tool, Inspect Devices.
转到更多工具，检查设备。
And that's going to pop up this window right here.
将会出现一个弹出窗口。
And I'm actually just going to zoom in a little bit,
我会放大一点
so you can see what's happening.
这样您可以查看发生了什么。
It's going to ask us if we want to forward one of our ports.
他会问我们是否要指导我们的一家门店。
I've already got Localhost 9000 set up here
我已经在这里安装了本地服务器9000
because that's the place where we're running our local server.
因为这是我们本地服务器运行的地方。
So put in Localhost 9000, go down and click Done.
因此，放置本地服务器9000，然后单击“完成”。
And over in this little box, we can just type in the URL
在这个小盒子上，我们可以写出网页的地址
that we'd like Chrome to open.
我们希望Chrom打开。
So I'll type in http://localhost9000.
因此，我将编写http：// localhost9000。
And if I've got Chrome running on my device, I can click Open.
如果我的设备上正在运行Chrome，则我将点击“打开”。
And now, you can see that we've actually
现在，您可以看到我们已经完成了
got the application running here on our phone.
在我们的手机上运行该应用。
And it looks really nice.
显示得很好。
All right.
知道了
So this is looking really great on my phone.
在我的手机上看起来很棒。
And more importantly, this is just a really useful debugging
更重要的是，这是一种修复技术
technique to know about.
她的知识很有用。
So if you're interested in learning more
因此，如果您有兴趣了解更多信息
about remote debugging, follow the link
关于远程维修
at the bottom of the screen.
请点击屏幕底部的链接。
Now, let's dive back in our code editor,
让我们回到脚本编辑器，
and we'll finish up our application.
我们将完成我们的应用程序的工作。
Now, switching back to our site, I'm
现在，回到我们的网站，
going to pop up in the dev tools.
我要开发工具。
And I'm going to boost the page up a little bit,
我将页面放大一点，
so it's easy to see what we're doing.
很容易看到我们在做什么。
And over here in our dev tools, I'm
在开发工具中
going to select the core header panel in the Elements tab.
我将从“项目”窗口中选择“基本横幅”面板。
If you recall, I mentioned before that there
如果您还记得的话，我之前说过有不同的情况
are various modes that we can put the header panel into.
我们可以将信签面板放入其中。
So to demonstrate this, I'm going to add an attribute here.
为了说明这一点，我将在此处添加一个属性。
And I'm going to give it a mode of scroll.
我将为其提供滚动模式。
And now, our toolbar is actually going
现在，我们的工具栏可以滚动了
to scroll with the rest of the content of the page.
与页面的其余内容。
Now, there's a few other modes that we
还有其他一些情况
can place the toolbar into.
我们也可以将它们放在工具栏中。
If we want, we can place it into a seamed mode.
如果需要，我们可以将它们放在重点位置。
What that's going to do is, it's going
他会做什么
to keep the toolbar sticky.
是这样可以保持工具栏稳定。
But you'll see that there's no longer a drop shadow
但是你会看到他不再投下阴影
as our content is scrolling underneath it.
我们的内容被传递了。
Another variation on this is, if we change the mode
另一个区别是，如果我们将情况更改为瀑布，
to Waterfall, the toolbar will start off in a seamed mode.
工具栏将以“安静”模式启动。
But as we scroll, you'll see that there's now
但是当您滚动时，您会注意到现在有一​​个阴影
and above the rest of the content.
并高于其余内容。
And there's one more mode that's actually pretty interesting.
还有另一个非常有趣的情况。
If we change it from Waterfall to Waterfall-Tall-- now,
如果我们把它从瀑布变成长瀑布，
pay attention to what happens here.
看结果。
--the toolbar itself gets a lot bigger.
工具栏本身变得更大。
And if you inspect the core toolbar element,
如果您已经检查了基础工具栏项目，
you'll see that it now has these two classes, Animate and Tall.
您会看到，现在他有这两类，搅拌和长度。
Basically, the header panel has reached in,
简而言之，信头面板伸展了
and it has told the toolbar that it
并告诉工具栏
should have these additional classes.
他必须要有两个新品种。
Now, if you remember from the last episode,
现在，如果我记得上一集，
we can add classes to the children of a core toolbar,
我们将项目添加到基本工具栏分支中，
to pin them to different locations.
将它们安装在不同的位置。
So if I open up my core header panel,
因此，如果您打开主横幅面板
find the title div inside of my toolbar,
然后在工具栏中搜索div标题，
then, I can actually give it some classes here.
然后，我实际上可以在这里提供一些项目。
I'm going to give it a bottom and indent class.
我会给它上课和下课的距离。
And you'll see now that the title of my application
您现在将看到我申请的标题
has kind of jumped to the bottom the toolbar.
在工具栏上向下移动。
It sort of indented over, so it has
他似乎弯曲了，
moved of the way of our Hamburger menu
所以他从汉堡包列表视图移到了
up here in the top left.
在左侧的顶部。
What's going to happen is, as we scroll the page,
将会发生的是，如果我们滚动页面，
you'll see that the toolbar collapses,
您会看到工具栏缩小，
and the title of our application moves with it.
我们应用程序的标题随之移动。
And this is a pretty wild effect, which you get basically
这是一个很好的效果，您可以免费获得
for free by adding an attribute and setting
通过添加属性
a few classes on your toolbar.
在工具栏中安装一些项目。
I think it's pretty neat.
我认为这做得很好。
All right.
知道了
There's one more mode for the header panel
标头面板有另一种模式
that I want to show you.
我想和你分享。
But we're going to need to hop back in our code editor
但是我们需要回去
So beck in our code editor, we're
因此，回到脚本编辑器，
going to set one final node on the header panel.
我们将在“横幅”面板中设置最后一个节点。
We're going to change its mode to Cover.
我们将其更改为大写字母。
And the Cover mode is going to take this content div,
加上封面将包含div内容，
and it's actually a float it visibly
它将鼓励她清楚地漂浮
on top of the core toolbar.
在主工具栏上方。
So to do this, we're going to open up our app CSS file.
为此，我们将为我们的应用程序打开一个CSS文件。
And I'm just going to drop in some CSS
我将做一些CSS
that I've already got saved here.
您已经保存在这里。
And I'll walk you through what's going on.
我将陪伴您发生的事情。
So we're selecting the core header panel,
我们选择主横幅面板，
and then, we're using this shadow so pseudo-element
然后我们使用这个假的阴影元素
to target its main container child.
以其主容器分支为目标。
And the main container child is where the content of our page
主容器分支是您在哪里
is actually being projected.
正在计划我们页面的内容。
So we're telling the content of the page
所以我们告诉页面的内容
to move over from the left edge of the screen by 180 pixels.
它从屏幕的左端移动约180像素。
Then, we're selecting the content element.
然后我们选择内容元素。
And we're telling it that we want
我们告诉他我们想要
to have a right margin of 180 pixels.
边距为180像素。
Now, I know this makes absolutely no sense
我知道这似乎不合逻辑
until you see what I'm doing in the screen.
这样您就可以在屏幕上看到我在做什么。
So let's hop back over to Chrome.
因此，让我们回到Chrome。
You'll see here that we've now got a page with our content
您会在这里看到我们现在有了一个包含我们内容的页面
with kind of like a medium gray background behind it.
后面带有浅灰色背景。
As were scrolling the page, the content
当我们滚动浏览页面时，
is actually visibly floating above the toolbar.
内容看起来清晰地漂浮在工具栏上方。
And on either side, we've got 180 pixels of space.
在侧面，我们有180像素的面积。
So it's a pretty interesting visual effect,
所以这是一个相当有趣的视觉效果，
and now, you know how to pull it off in your own app.
现在，您知道如何在自己的应用程序中进行操作了。
So in this video, we covered a lot
所以，在这部影片中
We've started down the path of composition
我们开始安装方式
by taking the header panel and combining it
通过采用刊头面板并将其与基本工具栏组合
We've gotten an application that looks
我们得到了申请
really great on our phone.
在移动设备上看起来很棒。
to show you one more element that you can combine
我会告诉您另一个可以包含的新项目
with the core header panel to make an experience that's
到基本刊头面板
We'll see you next time.
下次见。